[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Pablo Picasso is known for his contributions to the Cubist movement.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The Mona Lisa was painted by Vincent van Gogh.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Leonardo da Vinci created the sculpture 'David'.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Watercolor is a painting method that uses pigments suspended in a water-based solution.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Vincent van Gogh only sold one painting during his lifetime.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The Starry Night is a famous painting by Claude Monet.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The Sistine Chapel ceiling was painted by Michelangelo.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Jackson Pollock was a prominent figure in the Surrealist movement.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The painting 'The Persistence of Memory' features melting clocks and was created by Salvador Dal√≠.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Vincent van Gogh cut off his own ear.",
    "answer": true
  }
]
